What's this process been like this off
season getting ready for the NFL? Uh
it's been good. Just training, just
lifting, running,
getting your body ready to go do some
like indie and stuff like that. Make
sure you're hitting enough yardage and
things like that. So, been training with
Coach Schlegel. He's doing a great job
with that. He's former NFL strength
coach, so he kind of has an idea of what
that's going to look like. Now, when you
mix in with the visits with the teams,
does that complicate things for you?
Yeah, I mean, it can be a little, but
it's not too bad. You go in for maybe 2
days. You hydrate, train in the hotel.
You can make up for it. It's not too
bad. How much of a benefit do you think
you put being a former safety helps as
being a linebacker on the next level?
Yeah, I mean,
um
yeah, I mean, I think
the coverage responsibilities you're
asked to do at safety, at least for me,
my first 2 years, like I don't think
there's any coverage responsibility at
linebacker that's going to be harder
than that. So, I think it it gives me a
a big comfort level a level for like any
job I'm asked to do as a linebacker. I'm
fully comfortable with doing because
I've been asked to be a deep half, be a
deep post. I've been asked to cover a
slot receiver. So, I'm I'm fully
comfortable doing all these other jobs
I'm asked to do at the position. For
sure. You know, when you meet with
teams, what are you telling them they're
going to get in you?
I mean, I talk about my character, kind
of person I am. I talk about how I love
football, you know, being in the
building all the time, like a film
junkie kind of type of guy.
Um you know, I talk about being a guy
that's going to be bringing the locker
room together. Uh
you know, I feel like I can have that
effect.
At least I feel like I could do that
here at Ohio State. But I mean, it's
also surrounded by a bunch of great guys
here at Ohio State. But yeah, I just
talk I talk about who I am as a person.
And then I go on and talk about myself
as a player, you know. I think you let
the film talk for the most part, but at
times you got to describe yourself. Like
if I describe myself, I talk about being
versatile
>> [snorts]
>> and being able to do a multitude of
roles within the defense. You mentioned
Ohio State. What is it about Ohio State
that's able to churn out this level of
talent year after year after year?
>> Yeah, I think it's
it's just
I mean, it's like the brand. It's like
this we've been doing they've been doing
it here for so long despite who who's
been the coach, anything like that.
There's always good players here and
good and good men. I mean, I think Coach
Day especially has been doing a really
good job of bringing in not just really
talented players cuz in your Ohio State
you can recruit as many talented players
as you want, but bringing in really good
people. He's done an awesome job with
that.